A Guide to the Papers of Arthur W. Mitchell 1910-1950
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
Special Collections and Archives, Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
Arthur W. Mitchell Papers 1910-1950
Special Collections and Archives, Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
1910-1950
15,000 items
Copies of the family, personal, business and political correspondence of the first black Democratic Congressman in the United States. Mr. Mitchell represented Chicago in the United States House of Representatives from 1934-1942. The originals are housed at the Chicago Historical Society. Acc. #1968-15
Arthur W. Mitchell
Administrative Information
Access
There are no restrictions.
Biographical/Historical Information
Arthur W. Mitchell was born in Roanoke, Alabama, December 22, 1883 the son of Taylor and Ammar (Patterson) Mitchell, who were also natives of that state. Arthur W. Mitchell obtained his early education in Randolph and Chambers counties of Alabama, attending the public schools, and afterward entered the Snow Hill Industrial School and Tuskegee Normal and Industrial Institute at Tuskegee, Alabama in 1899.
He subsequently taught in the public schools of Alabama, and during this time he established the Armstrong Agricultural School in 1908 at West Butler, Alabama, and served as its principal until he resigned in 1917 to enter military training at Camp Pike, Arkansas. In 1919 he moved to Washington, D.C, read law, for a period of three years, during which time he also engaged in the real estate business. In 1924 he moved to Chicago and was admitted to the practice of law in the State of Illinois.
In 1934 he was selected by the regular Democratic Organization to become the candidate for congress from the first Illinois district and was elected to the congress of the United States House of Representatives, becoming the first African-American elected to the House as a Democrat. Mitchell was reelected in 1936, 1938, and 1940, thus serving four full terms and retired in January 1943.
After retirement Arthur Mitchell moved to Dinwiddie County, Virginia where he built a southern style mansion, in which he enjoyed the life of being a southern gentlemen. His hopes for a political career in Virginia did not come to be. He continued as President of The Mutual Housing Company and was one of the individuals who established Virginians against Jim Crow.
Arthur Mitchell was married several times, in 1904 he married his first wife Eula King and they had a child Arthur W. Mitchell Jr. His first wife Eula King died in 1909, he then married Annie H. Harris in 1911.
Scope and Content Information
When Arthur Mitchell was elected he became the Black Congressional Representative of African-Americans. Mitchell deeply resented this and this is reflected in his correspondence. Nevertheless, African- American and others sought his help and support for a number of different agendas.
Correspondence and speeches in this manuscript group document quite clearly the friction between Mitchell and many Americans. Of particular note. correspondence documenting Mitchell long fight with the NAACP over a national Anti-Lynch law and his Controversial "Negro Commission". Most of the correspondence is with the Chicago Democratic Party and concerns political patronage.
Some correspondence with William Hastie, Henry Stimson, Walter White, Roy Wilkins, William Dawson and others.
Series Description
Series I. Family And Personal Correspondence 1910, 1965 A. Family 1932, 1965 Correspondence between Mitchell and family members. B. Personal 1910, 1934 Subjects concerning a wide range of issues. C. "Miss B" 1935-1943 Correspondence with a special person in Mr. Mitchell's life.
Series II. Congressional Correspondence A. Interoffice 1935-1941 Mitchell corresponding with his office staff. B. Congressional 1935- 1942 Mostly matters pertaining to Party politics. A large number of letters from people seeking jobs and other political favors. Arranged chronologically within the folders. Correspondence about Lynching and the Negro Industrial Community.
Series III. Correspondence Post Congressional from a number of individuals seeking assistance and Hoping that Mitchell as an ex-congressman can provide it. A. General Correspondence by date 1942-1968 B. Correspondence N.D., Alpha
Series IV. The Mutual Housing Co. 1920-1957 Mitchell established the Mutual Housing Company soon after his arrival in Washington D.C. The series has minutes, financial statements, deeds, and correspondence. A. Ledgers and Reports Minutes, proposals and articles of incorporations B. Minutes 1920-1924
Series V. Mitchell v. The United States. Arthurs lawsuit against the Illinois Central Railroad.
Series VI. Literary A. Reports B. Writing Articles C. Speeches
Series VII. Printed A. Political Broadsides B. News Clippings
Box List
- Family and Personal
  - Family 1932,1965
    - Family Correspondence 1932 (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Family Correspondence 1940-1945 (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Funeral Bill 1965 (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Family Correspondence 1946-1949 (Box-folder 1:4)
    - Family 1950-1966 and N.D. (Box-folder 1:5)
    - Family Correspondence 1934 Oct 16-31 (Box-folder 2:1)
    - Family Correspondence 1934 Nov 1-7 (Box-folder 2:2)
    - Family Correspondence 1934 Nov 8-9 (Box-folder 2:3)
    - Family Correspondence 1934 Nov 10-12 (Box-folder 2:4)
    - Family Correspondence 1933 (Box-folder 2:5)
    - Family Correspondence 1934 Jan (Box-folder 2:6)
    - Family Correspondence 1934 Feb (Box-folder 2:7)
    - Family Correspondence 1934 March (Box-folder 2:8)
    - Family Correspondence 1934 April (Box-folder 2:9)
    - Family Correspondence 1934 May (Box-folder 2:10)
    - Family Correspondence 1934 June (Box-folder 2:11)
    - Family Correspondence 1934 July (Box-folder 2:12)
    - Family Correspondence 1932 (Box-folder 2:13)
  - Personal 1910,1934
    - Personal Correspondence 1910,1929 (Box-folder 2:14)
    - Personal Correspondence 1934 August (Box-folder 2:15)
    - Personal Correspondence 1934 September (Box-folder 2:16)
    - Personal Correspondence 1934 Oct (Box-folder 2:17)
    - Personal Correspondence 1934 Nov 13-15 (Box-folder 3:1)
    - Personal Correspondence 1934 Nov 16-19 (Box-folder 3:2)
    - Personal Correspondence 1934 Nov 20-22 (Box-folder 3:3)
    - Personal Correspondence 1934 Nov 23-24 (Box-folder 3:4)
    - Personal Correspondence 1934 Nov 25-26 (Box-folder 3:5)
    - Personal Correspondence 1934 Nov 27-30 (Box-folder 3:6)
    - Personal Correspondence 1934 Dec 1-5 (Box-folder 3:7)
    - Personal Correspondence 1934 Dec 6-7 (Box-folder 3:8)
    - Personal Correspondence 1934 Dec 8-10 (Box-folder 3:9)
    - Personal Correspondence 1934 Dec 11-15 (Box-folder 3:10)
    - Personal Correspondence 1934 Dec 16-19 (Box-folder 3:11)
    - Personal Correspondence 1934 Dec 20-24 (Box-folder 3:12)
    - Personal Correspondence 1934 Dec 26-28 (Box-folder 3:13)
    - Personal Correspondence 1934 Dec 29-31 (Box-folder 3:14)
  - Miss B
    - Miss B 1935,1939 (Box-folder 4:1)
    - Miss B 1940,1943 (Box-folder 4:2)
    - Miss B, 4:3
- Congressional Correspondence
  - Interoffice 1935-1941
    - Interoffice Correspondence 1935 (Box-folder 5:1)
    - Interoffice Correspondence 1936 (Box-folder 5:2)
    - Interoffice Correspondence 1937 (Box-folder 5:3)
    - Interoffice Correspondence 1938 (Box-folder 5:4)
    - Interoffice Correspondence 1939 (Box-folder 5:5)
    - Interoffice Correspondence 1940 (Box-folder 5:6)
    - Interoffice Correspondence 1941 (Box-folder 5:7)
  - Congressional 1935-1942
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Jan 1-5 (Box-folder 6:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Jan 6-8 (Box-folder 6:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Jan 9-10 (Box-folder 6:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Jan 11 (Box-folder 6:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Jan 12-15 (Box-folder 6:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Jan 16-17 (Box-folder 6:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Jan 18-20 (Box-folder 6:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Jan 21-22 (Box-folder 6:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Jan 23-24 (Box-folder 6:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Jan 25-26 (Box-folder 6:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Jan 27-31 (Box-folder 6:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Feb 1-4 (Box-folder 7:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Feb 5-6 (Box-folder 7:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Feb 7-11 (Box-folder 7:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Feb 12-14 (Box-folder 7:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Feb 15 (Box-folder 7:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Feb 16-19 (Box-folder 7:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Feb 20-22 (Box-folder 7:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Feb 23-28 (Box-folder 7:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 March 1-3 (Box-folder 7:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 March 4-5 (Box-folder 7:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 March 6-10 (Box-folder 7:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 March 11-13 (Box-folder 8:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 March 14-18 (Box-folder 8:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 March 19-21 (Box-folder 8:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 March 22-25 (Box-folder 8:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 March 26-27 (Box-folder 8:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 March 28-31 (Box-folder 8:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 April 1-4 (Box-folder 8:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 April 5-10 (Box-folder 8:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 April 11-15 (Box-folder 8:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 April 16-19 (Box-folder 8:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 April 20-25 (Box-folder 9:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 April 26-30 (Box-folder 9:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 May 1-5 (Box-folder 9:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 May 6-10 (Box-folder 9:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 May 11-15 (Box-folder 9:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 May 16-19 (Box-folder 9:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 May 20-21 (Box-folder 9:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 May 22-25 (Box-folder 9:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 May 26-28 (Box-folder 9:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 May 29-31 (Box-folder 9:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 June 1-5 (Box-folder 9:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 June 6-10 (Box-folder 9:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 June 18-21 (Box-folder 10:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 June 22-30 (Box-folder 10:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 July 1-5 (Box-folder 10:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 July 6-10 (Box-folder 10:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 July 11-15 (Box-folder 10:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 June 11-17 (Box-folder 10:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional June 18-21 (Box-folder 10:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 June 22-30 (Box-folder 10:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 July 1-5 (Box-folder 10:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 July 6-10 (Box-folder 10:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 July 11-15 (Box-folder 10:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 July 16-19 (Box-folder 10:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 July 20-25 (Box-folder 10:13)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 July 26-31 (Box-folder 10:14)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Aug 1-10 (Box-folder 10:15)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Aug 11-19 (Box-folder 10:16)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Aug 21-30 (Box-folder 10:17)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Sept 1-10 (Box-folder 11:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Sept 11-15 (Box-folder 11:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Sept 16-19 (Box-folder 11:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Sept 20-30 (Box-folder 11:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Oct 1-15 (Box-folder 11:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Oct 16-31 (Box-folder 11:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Nov (Box-folder 11:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Dec 1-10 (Box-folder 11:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Dec 11-19 (Box-folder 11:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Dec 20-31 (Box-folder 11:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1935 Frags (Box-folder 11:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Jan 1-5 (Box-folder 12:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Jan 6-10 (Box-folder 12:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Jan 11-15 (Box-folder 12:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Jan 16-19 (Box-folder 12:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Jan 20-25 (Box-folder 12:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Jan 26-28 (Box-folder 12:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Jan 29 (Box-folder 12:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Jan 30-31 (Box-folder 12:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Feb 1-3 (Box-folder 12:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Feb 4-5 (Box-folder 12:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Feb 6-10 (Box-folder 12:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Feb 11-12 (Box-folder 12:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Feb 13-15 (Box-folder 12:13)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Feb 16-19 (Box-folder 13:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Feb 20-25 (Box-folder 13:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Feb 26-29 (Box-folder 13:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Mar 1-4 (Box-folder 13:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Mar 5-10 (Box-folder 13:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Mar 11-15 (Box-folder 13:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Mar 16-19 (Box-folder 13:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Mar 20-25 (Box-folder 13:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Mar 26-31 (Box-folder 13:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 April 1-15 (Box-folder 13:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 April 6-10 (Box-folder 13:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 April 11-15 (Box-folder 13:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 April 16-19 (Box-folder 13:13)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 April 20-22 (Box-folder 14:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 April 23-24 (Box-folder 14:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 April 25-27 (Box-folder 14:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 April 28-30 (Box-folder 14:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 May 1-5 (Box-folder 14:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 May 6-10 (Box-folder 14:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 May 11-15 (Box-folder 14:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 May 16-20 (Box-folder 14:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 May 21-23 (Box-folder 14:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 May 25-31 (Box-folder 14:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 June 1-4 (Box-folder 14:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 June 5-15 (Box-folder 14:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 June 16-19 (Box-folder 14:13)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 June 20-30 (Box-folder 15:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 July 1-15 (Box-folder 15:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 July 16-24 (Box-folder 15:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 July 25-31 (Box-folder 15:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Aug 1-3 (Box-folder 15:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Aug 4-5 (Box-folder 15:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Aug 6-7 (Box-folder 15:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Aug 8-10 (Box-folder 15:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Aug 11-15 (Box-folder 15:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Aug 16-25 (Box-folder 15:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Aug 26-27 (Box-folder 15:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Aug 28-31 (Box-folder 15:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Sept 1-3 (Box-folder 16:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Sept 4-5 (Box-folder 16:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Sept 6-10 (Box-folder 16:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Sept 11-15 (Box-folder 16:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Sept 16-17 (Box-folder 16:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Sept 18-19 (Box-folder 16:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Sept 20-21 (Box-folder 16:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Sept 22-23 (Box-folder 16:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Sept 24 (Box-folder 16:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Sept 25-28 (Box-folder 16:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Sept 29-31 (Box-folder 16:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Oct 1-2 (Box-folder 17:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Oct 3-5 (Box-folder 17:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Oct 6-7 (Box-folder 17:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Oct 8 (Box-folder 17:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Oct 9-10 (Box-folder 17:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Oct 11-13 (Box-folder 17:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Oct 14-15 (Box-folder 17:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Oct 16 (Box-folder 17:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Oct 17-19 (Box-folder 17:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Oct 20-21 (Box-folder 17:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Oct 22 (Box-folder 17:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Oct 23-25 (Box-folder 18:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Oct 26-27 (Box-folder 18:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Oct 28-31 (Box-folder 18:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Nov 1-2 (Box-folder 18:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Nov 4-5 (Box-folder 18:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Nov 6-8 (Box-folder 18:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Nov 9-10 (Box-folder 18:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Nov 11-20 (Box-folder 18:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Nov 21-30 (Box-folder 18:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Dec 1-10 (Box-folder 18:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1936 Dec 11-31 (Box-folder 18:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Jan 1-4 (Box-folder 19:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Jan 5-6 (Box-folder 19:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Jan 7-9 (Box-folder 19:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Jan 10-13 (Box-folder 19:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Jan 14-15 (Box-folder 19:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Jan 16-18 (Box-folder 19:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Jan 19-21 (Box-folder 19:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Jan 22-25 (Box-folder 19:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Jan 26-27 (Box-folder 19:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Jan 28-31 (Box-folder 19:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Feb 1-5 (Box-folder 19:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Feb 6-10 (Box-folder 19:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Feb 11-12 (Box-folder 19:13)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Feb 13-15 (Box-folder 19:14)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Feb 16 (Box-folder 20:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Feb 17 (Box-folder 20:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Feb 18-19 (Box-folder 20:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Feb 20-22 (Box-folder 20:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Feb 23-24 (Box-folder 20:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Feb 25 (Box-folder 20:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Feb 26-28 (Box-folder 20:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Feb 26-28 (Box-folder 20:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Mar 6-8 (Box-folder 20:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Mar 9-10 (Box-folder 20:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Mar 11-12 (Box-folder 20:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Mar 13-15 (Box-folder 20:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Mar 16-19 (Box-folder 20:13)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Mar 20-23 (Box-folder 20:14)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Mar 24-28 (Box-folder 21:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Mar 29-31 (Box-folder 21:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 April 1-3 (Box-folder 21:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 April 4-5 (Box-folder 21:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 April 6-10 (Box-folder 21:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 April 11-13 (Box-folder 21:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 April 14-19 (Box-folder 21:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 April 20-30 (Box-folder 21:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 May 1-10 (Box-folder 21:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 May 11-15 (Box-folder 21:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 May 16-19 (Box-folder 21:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 May 20-25 (Box-folder 21:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 May 26-31 (Box-folder 21:13)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 June 1-5 (Box-folder 22:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 June 6-10 (Box-folder 22:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 June 11-15 (Box-folder 22:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 June 16-20 (Box-folder 22:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 June 21-28 (Box-folder 22:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 June 29-31 (Box-folder 22:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 July 1-10 (Box-folder 22:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 July 11-16 (Box-folder 22:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 July 17-20 (Box-folder 22:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 July 21-25 (Box-folder 22:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 July 26-31 (Box-folder 22:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Aug 1-10 (Box-folder 22:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 July 11-19 (Box-folder 22:13)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 July 20-31 (Box-folder 22:14)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Sept 1-10 (Box-folder 22:15)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Sept 11-30 (Box-folder 22:16)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Oct 1-10 (Box-folder 22:17)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Oct 11-19 (Box-folder 23:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Oct 20-25 (Box-folder 23:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Oct 26-31 (Box-folder 23:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Nov 1-10 (Box-folder 23:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Nov 11-20 (Box-folder 23:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Nov 21-31 (Box-folder 23:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Dec 1-10 (Box-folder 23:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Dec 11-20 (Box-folder 23:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1937 Dec 21-31 (Box-folder 23:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Jan 1-10 (Box-folder 23:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Jan 11-13 (Box-folder 23:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Jan 14-17 (Box-folder 23:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Jan 18-20 (Box-folder 23:13)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Jan 21-31 (Box-folder 23:14)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Feb 1-5 (Box-folder 24:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Feb 6-10 (Box-folder 24:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Feb 11-16 (Box-folder 24:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Feb 17-19 (Box-folder 24:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Feb 20-23 (Box-folder 24:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Feb 24-28 (Box-folder 24:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Mar 1-5 (Box-folder 24:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Mar 6-10 (Box-folder 24:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Mar 11-15 (Box-folder 24:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Mar 16-19 (Box-folder 24:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Mar 20-25 (Box-folder 24:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 mar 26-31 (Box-folder 24:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 april 1-10 (Box-folder 25:1)